Mss.Ms.Coll.137
American Philosophical Society
- IV. Works by Others, 1934-2005; 3.0 Linear feet (Box 24-29)
  - Plan for Meta-Analysis of Summer School/Programs, 2000; Kim, James S. (Box 27)
  - Summer Reading and the Achievement Gap, 2003; Kim, James S. (Box 27)
  - Summer Reading, Summer Programs, and the Achievement Gap, 2002; Kim, James S. (Box 27)
  - And Quiet Flows the Don through the Computer, 1978; Kjetsaa, Geir, 1937- (Box 27)
    Association for Literary and Linguistic Computing Bulletin, Vol. 7
  - Data Driven Generating Functions and a Short Proof of Fermat's Last Theorem, 2000; Klawansky, Sidney (Box 27)
  - Rejection, Motivation, and Athletic Performance: Is There a Traded Player Syndrome?, 1977-1978; Kopelman, Richard E.; Pantaleno, James J. (Box 27)
    Reprint from Perceptual and Motor Skills, Vol. 45, and letter from Mosteller.
  - Reassessing the View that American Schools are Broken, 1998; Krueger, Alan B. (Box 27)
  - Effect of Attending a Small Class in the Early Grades on College-Test Taking and Middle School Test Results: Evidence from Project STAR, 1999; Krueger, Alan B.; Whitmore, Diane M. (Box 27)
  - Frederick Mosteller, President-Elect, 1979; Kruskal, William, 1919-2005 (Box 27)
  - Leonard Jimmie Savage, 1975; Kruskal, William, 1919-2005 (Box 27)
  - Approximate Posterior Distributions for Incomplete Data Problems, 1980; Laird, Nan M., 1943-; Louis, Thomas A., 1944- (Box 27)
  - Observations and Materials on the History of Quantification in Sociology, 1959; Lazarsfeld, Paul Felix (Box 27)
  - A Hand Search of the American Educational Research Journal from 1964-1998: Articles on Meta-Analyses, Randomized Experiments, Quasi-Experiments, and Observational/Correlational Studies in Math and Science Education, 2000; Leow, Christine S. (Box 27)
  - Statistical Inference, 1953; Lindley, D. V., (Dennis Victor), b. 1923 (Box 27)
    Annotated reprint from Journal of the Royal Statistical Society, Series B (Methodological), Vol. 15, No. 1
  - Bayesian Statistics, 1964; Locke, Laurance G. (Box 27)
  - Summary of the Global Burden of Disease, 1996; Lopez, Alan D.; Murray, Christopher J. L. (Box 27)
  - Some Comments on Bayesian Methods, 1970; Mallows, Colin L (Box 27)
    From Meyer and Collier (eds.), Bayesian Statistics
  - Some Principles of Data Analysis, 1987; Mallows, Colin L; Pregibon, Daryl (Box 27)
    Invited Paper 26.1, 46th Session of the ISI
  - Handout for Statistical Studies in Genetic Toxicology, 1985; Margolin, Barry H. (Box 28)
  - Syndromic Surveillance: Is it Worth the Effort?, 2004; Mariano, Louis T.; Schonlau, Matthias; Stoto, Michael A. (Box 28)
    Annotated reprint from Chance, Vol. 17, No. 1
  - Rigorous Uncertainty: Why RA Fisher is Important, 2002; Marks, Harry M., 1947- (Box 28)
  - Cost Benefit Analysis - Cost Effectiveness Analysis, n.d.; McPeek, Bucknam, 1933- (Box 28)
  - Making Single Mothers Work: Recent Tax and Welfare Policy and its Effects, 2000; Meyer, Bruce D.; Rosenbaum, Dan T. (Box 28)
  - Asymptotic Theory of Selection by Relative Rank with High Cost, 1993; Moriguchi, Shigeichi, b. 1916 (Box 28)
    Journal of the Operations Research Society of Japan, Vol. 36, No. 4
  - Asymptotic Theory of Selection by Relative Rank with Low Cost, 1993; Moriguchi, Shigeichi, b. 1916 (Box 28)
    Journal of the Operations Research Society of Japan, Vol. 36, No. 3
  - Asymptotic Theory of Selection by Relative Rank with Medium Cost, 1993; Moriguchi, Shigeichi, b. 1916 (Box 28)
    Journal of the Operations Research Society of Japan, Vol. 36, No. 2
  - Basic Theory of Selection by Relative Rank with Cost, 1993; Moriguchi, Shigeichi, b. 1916 (Box 28)
    Journal of the Operations Research Society of Japan, Vol. 36, No. 1
  - Selection Problem with Cost - Secretary Problem when Unlimited Recall is Allowed, 1992; Moriguchi, Shigeichi, b. 1916 (Box 28)
    Journal of the Operations Research Society of Japan, Vol. 35, No. 4
  - Home Field Advantages and the Seventh Game World Series Phenomenon, 1976; Morrison, Donald G. (Box 28)
    New York Statistician, Vol. 28, No. 2
  - Literary Detection: How to Prove Authorship and Fraud in Literature and Documents, 1978; Morton, A. Q., (Andrew Queen) (Box 28)
    Typed review and photocopied excerpts
  - Measuring Pitcher Performance in Baseball or A Better Way than the ERA, 1978; Moy, Kenneth (Box 28)
  - Moyens Statistiques et Problemes d'Attribution de Textes Anonymes, Muller, Charles (Box 28)
    From Etudes de Linguistique Appliquee
  - Changing World of Employment: Factory Jobs, Productivity, and Worker Quality, 2004; National Research Council (U.S.). Committee on National Statistics.; Norwood, Janet Lippe (Box 28)
  - Behavioral and Social Sciences and Education at the National Academies, National Research Council (U.S.). Division of Behavioral and Social Sciences and Education. (Box 28)
  - Standards of Evidence and the Quality of Behavioral and Social Science Research, 2004; National Research Council (U.S.). Division of Behavioral and Social Sciences and Education. (Box 28)
  - Science as a Source of Political Conflict, 1979; Nelkin, Dorothy (Box 28)
    From Segerstedt (ed.), Ethics for Science Policy
  - Problems and Procedures in the Regulation of Technological Risk From Weiss (ed.), Making Bureaucracies Work, 1979; Nelkin, Dorothy; Pollak, Michael (Box 28)
  - Stylistic Analysis, 1980; Oakman, Robert L., 1941- (Box 28)
    From Oakman, Computer Methods for Literary Research
  - Evaluating Offensive Performance in Baseball, Circa 1976; Pankin, Mark D. (Box 28)
  - Television and Sports, 1977; Parente, Donald (Box 28)
  - Some Incidents in the Early History of Biometry and Statistics, 1890-1894, 1961; Pearson, E. S., (Egon Sharpe), 1895-1980 (Box 28)
  - Biblical Texts and Statistical Analysis: Zechariah and Beyond, 1984; Petersen, David L.; Portnoy, Stephen (Box 28)
    Manuscript copy and reprint from Journal of Biblical Literature, Vol. 103, No. 1
  - Genesis, Wellhausen and the Computer: A Response, 1983; Petersen, David L.; Portnoy, Stephen (Box 28)
  - How Can We Respond Effectively to Juvenile Crime?, 2000; Petrosino, Anthony J. (Box 28)
  - Professional and Curriculum Vita, 2002; Petrosino, Anthony J. (Box 28)
  - Progress Toward a Register of Reviews Relevant to Criminology and Criminal Justice, 2000; Petrosino, Anthony J. (Box 28)
  - What Works Revisited Again: A Systematic Review of 300 Randomized Field Trials in Crime Reduction, 2002; Petrosino, Anthony J. (Box 28)
  - Statistics and Religious Studies, Circa 1984; Portnoy, Stephen (Box 28)
  - Bayesian Interpretation of Standard Inference Statements, 1964; Pratt, John W. (John Winsor), 1931- (Box 28)
  - Probability in Mathematics and Statistics: A Century's Predictor of Future Directions, 1992; Pyke, R., (Ronald) (Box 28)
  - Meta-Analysis of Interventions to Decrease Disruptive Classroom Behavior in Public Education Settings, 1997; Quiroz, David R.; Stage, Scott A. (Box 28)
    Annotated reprint from School Psychology Review, Vol. 26, No. 3
  - Definite Article: A Type And/Or Author-Specifying Discriminant in the Hebrew Bible, 1976; Radday, Yehuda Thomas; Shore, H. (Box 28)
    Association for Literary and Linguistic Computing, Vol. 4
  - Strategies of Data Analysis, 1987; Rao, C. Radhakrishna (Calyampudi Radhakrishna), 1920- (Box 28)
  - Animated Word: Modification of Meaning by Context, 1980; Reyna, Valerie F., 1955- (Box 28)
  - Language of Possibility and Probability: Effects of Negation on Meaning, Reyna, Valerie F., 1955- (Box 28)
  - Bayesian Inference, 1963; Roberts, Harry V. (Box 28)
  - Bayesian Inferences for Dichotomous Finite Populations, Simple Random Sampling, 1964; Roberts, Harry V. (Box 28)
  - College for All: Do Students Understand what College Demands, 1998; Rosenbaum, James E., 1943- (Box 28)
  - Interpersonal Expectancy Effects: The First 345 Studies, 1978; Rosenthal, Robert, 1933-; Rubin, Donald B. (Box 28)
  - Analysis of Professional Football Scores, 1976; Rosner, Bernard, (Bernard A.) (Box 28)
    From Machol et al (eds.), Management Science in Sports
  - Comparison of Physical and Behavioral Science: The Roles of Theory, Measurement, and Effect Size, 1985; Rossi, Joseph S. (Box 28)
  - Effect of Inadequate Statistical Power on Specific Research Literatures, 1986; Rossi, Joseph S. (Box 28)
    Letter and manuscript
  - Inadequate Statistical Power: A Source of Artifactual Controversy in Behavioral Research, 1983; Rossi, Joseph S. (Box 29)
  - Meta-Analysis, Power Analysis, and Artifactual Controversy: The Case of Spontaneous Recovery of Verbal Associations, 1982; Rossi, Joseph S. (Box 29)
  - Surveys of Statistical Power, n.d.; Rossi, Joseph S. (Box 29)
  - Bayesianly Justifiable and Relevant Frequency Calculations for the Applied Statistician, 1984; Rubin, Donald B. (Box 29)
    Reprint from Annals of Statistics, Vol. 12, No. 4; with notes.
  - Estimation from Nonrandomized Treatment Comparisons using Subclassification on Propensity Scores, 1998; Rubin, Donald B. (Box 29)
  - Recommended Format for Protocol for Clinical Research Program. Clinical Comparison of Several Anterior and Posterior Restorative Materials, 1977; Ryge, Gunnar; Stanford, J. W. (Box 29)
  - Sustained Benefits in Education: The Role of Early Intervention in School Dropout, 1997; Sachs, Jason A. (Box 29)
    Manuscript drafts and correspondence.
  - Bias in Analytic Research, 1979; Sackett, David L. (Box 29)
    Annotated reprint from Journal of Chronic Diseases, Vol. 32
  - Bayesian Operating Characteristic Curves for Reliability and Quality Sampling Plans, 1964; Schafer, R. E. (Box 29)
    Industrial Quality Control, Vol. 21, No. 3
  - On Bayes Procedures, 1965; Schwartz, Lorraine (Box 29)
    Z. Wahrscheinlichkeitstheorie, Vol. 4
  - Multiple Hypothesis Testing: A Review, 1994; Shaffer, Juliet Popper (Box 29)
  - Bayes Estimation of Proportions: The Effect of Stimulus Distribution and Exposure Time, 1959; Shuford, Emir Hamvasy, b. 1929; Wiesen, Raymond A. (Box 29)
  - Fortieth Anniversary of the Council's Pre-election Polls of 1948, 1988; Sills, David L. (Box 29)
    Items, Vol. 42, No. 4
  - Sentence Length and Statistical Linguistics, 1963; Spang-Hanssen, Henning (Box 29)
  - Toward Conducting Benefit-Cost Analysis of Data Programs, 1984; Spencer, Bruce D. (Box 29)
  - Fisher in 1921, 2004; Stigler, Stephen M. (Box 29)
  - Isaac Newton as a Probabilist, 2005; Stigler, Stephen M. (Box 29)
  - Problematic Unity of Biometrics, 2000; Stigler, Stephen M. (Box 29)
  - Response to Hanna H. Gray's The University in History, 2001; Stigler, Stephen M. (Box 29)
  - Did Knives and Forks Cut Murders?, 2003; Stille, Alexander (Box 29)
  - What to do when the Experts Disagree, 1982; Stoto, Michael A. (Box 29)
  - Laboratory of Social Relations, Harvard University. Report for the Five Years 1946-1951, Stouffer, Samuel Andrew, 1900-1960 (Box 29)
  - Review of the Quality of Reported Information for the Assessment of Efficacy and Safety of Therapy, 1983; Stryker, Scott (Box 29)
  - Bayesian Analysis of Random-Effect Models in the Analysis of Variance. II. Effect of Autocorrelated Errors, 1965; Tan, W. Y., 1934-; Tiao, George C., 1933- (Box 29)
  - Five-Hundred Life-Saving Interventions and Their Cost-Effectiveness, 1994-1995; Tengs, Tammy O. et al (Box 29)
    Manuscript copy and reprint from Risk Analysis, Vol. 15, No. 3
  - Bayesian Analysis of the Regression Model with Autocorrelated Errors, 1963; Tiao, George C., 1933-; Zellner, Arnold (Box 29)
  - On the Bayesian Estimation of Multivariate Regression, 1963; Tiao, George C., 1933-; Zellner, Arnold (Box 29)
  - Use of CONSTAT in Authorship Investigations, 1975; Ule, L. A. (Box 29)
    Association for Literary and Linguistic Computing Bulletin
  - Women in the University of Chicago. Report of the Committee on University Women, 1970; University of Chicago. Committee on University Women. (Box 29)
  - Definition of Research Raises Concerns, 2000; Viadero, Debra (Box 29)
  - What is (and isn't) Research?, 1999; Viadero, Debra (Box 29)
  - Frequency of Frequencies, 1970; Weisberg, Sanford, 1947- (Box 29)
  - When Money Matters: How Educational Expenditures Improve Student Performance and How they Don't, 1997; Wenglinsky, Harold (Box 29)
  - On Disputed Authorship, Statistically, 1976; Wickmann, D. (Box 29)
  - Picasso and the Cuban Missile Crisis, 2001; Wiener, Malcolm H. (Box 29)
    Reprint from Apollo, October 2001
  - Shakespeare versus Bacon: Parallels, 2002; Wigston, William Francis C. (Box 29)
  - Statistical Aspects of Experiments in Telepathy, 1936; Wilks, S. S., (Samuel Stanley), 1906-1964 (Box 29)
  - Mendenhall's Studies of Word-Length Distribution in the Works of Shakespeare and Bacon, 1975; Williams, C. B. (Box 29)
    Biomterika, Vol. 62, No. 1. Includes typed notes
  - Style and Vocabulary: Numerical Studies, 1970; Williams, C. B. (Box 29)
  - Modified Play-the-Winner Rule for Sequential Trials, 1976; Wong, George (Box 29)
  - Some Aspects of Significance Testing with Data-Peeking Allowed, 1976; Wong, George (Box 29)
  - Contingency Tables Involving Small Numbers and the X 2 Test, 1934; Yates, F. (Box 29)
    Annotated reprint from Royal Statistical Society, Suppl. 1
  - Exploratory Data Analysis in the Development Stage of New Products, 1987; Yoshizawa, Tadashi (Box 29)
    Invited Paper 5.3, 46th Session of the ISI
  - Problems of Conducting Clinical Trials in Cancer1, 1969; Zelen, Marvin (Box 29)
- V. Memoranda, 1969-1990; 2.0 Linear feet (Box 30-33)
  - National Science Foundation Memoranda, 1969-1990; 108.0 folders (Box 30-33)
    - Memorandum NS-130. Preface to the Soviet Edition of Fifty Challenging Problems in Probability, 1969; 100; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-299. Who Won Anyway? A Statistical Analysis of Election Recounts, 1975; Israels, Michael J. (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-323. Empirical Bayes Example: Maximum Likelihood Estimate of Normal Prior with Normal Data Distribution, Illustrated by an Application to Surgery Data, 1976; Gilbert, John P.; Laird, Nan M., 1943-; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Parunak, Anita (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-324. Empirical Bayes Example: Estimating a Discrete Prior Distribution in the Presence of a Normal Data Distribution, Illustrated by an Application to Surgery Data, 1976; Gilbert, John P.; Laird, Nan M., 1943-; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Parunak, Anita (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-325. Empirical Bayes Example: Estimating a Discrete Prior in the Presence of a Normal Data Distribution, Artificial Examples, 1976; Gilbert, John P.; Laird, Nan M., 1943-; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Parunak, Anita (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-326. Non-Parametric Maximum Likelihood Estimation of a Distribution Function and Self-Consistency, 1976; Laird, Nan M., 1943- (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-327. Play-the-Winner Rule and Clinical Trials, 1976; Wong, George (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-331. Randomization with Balancing in Clinical Trials, 1976; Parunak, Anita (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-368. Work Done Before 1960 on Combining Tests of Significance, 1977; Gitter, Natasha (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-369. Continuation of the Work Done Before 1960 on the Topic of Combining Tests of Significance, 1977; Gitter, Natasha (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-370. Works Done on Combining Tests of Signficance from 1971-1976, 1978; Romanowicz, Nancy (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-371. Continuation of Survey of Works on Combining Statistics in 1960-1976, 1978; Romanowicz, Nancy (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-372. Summary of the Work Done Between 1960 and 1970 on the Topic of Combining Tests of Significance, 1978; Gitter, Natasha (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-373. Further Papers on Combining Independent Tests of Significance, 1978; Gitter, Natasha (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-488. Description or Prediction?, 1984; Hoaglin, David C. (David Caster), 1944-; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-512. First Look at Response Reversals, 1985; Kong, Augustine (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-523. 3rd Draft of the Probability Expression Paper, 1985; Kong, Augustine (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-525. How Medical Professionals Evaluate Expressions for Probabilities, 1985; Barnett, G. Octo; Kong, Augustine; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-529. Search for Reports on Quantification of Verbal Expressions, 1985; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-542. Memo on Probabililty Terminology Study, 1986; Reagan, Robert Timothy (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-545. Issues to be Considered in Planning a Survey of the Quantitative Meanings of Probabilistic Words, 1986; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Reagan, Robert Timothy (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-546. Selection of Probability Expressions for a Survey of Quantitative Meanings, 1986; Reagan, Robert Timothy (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-547. Thoughts Regarding the Format of a Survey of Quantitative Meanings of Probability Expressions, 1986; Reagan, Robert Timothy (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-557. Point Estimates for Probability Expressions, 1986; Reagan, Robert Timothy (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-559. Quantitative Meanings of Probability Expressions: Pilot Data, 1986; Reagan, Robert Timothy (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-562. Reflections on Issues to be Considered in Planning a Survey of the Quantitative Meanings of Verbal Probability Expressions, 1986; Reagan, Robert Timothy (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-564. Which Denominator for which Line?, 1986; Blackwell, T. E., (Thomas E.) (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-577. How Medical Professionals Evaluate Expressions for Probabilities, 1986; Barnett, G. Octo; Kong, Augustine; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-580. Questionnaire Designed for Science Writers, 1986; Kong, Augustine (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-593. Pilot Study on Probability Expressions`, 1986; Kong, Augustine (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-613. Report on a Word Probability Study, 1987; Reagan, Robert Timothy (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-615. Numerical Meanings of Probabilistic Expressions: Questionnaire Sent to Science Writers, 1987; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-635. Numerical Meanings of Probabilistic Expressions -- Questionnaire, 1987; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-636. Numerical Meanings of Probabilistic Expressions -- Medians of Your Own Best Estimate, 1987; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-637. Numerical Meanings of Probabilistic Expressions -- Distributions of Your Own Best Estimate, 1987; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-638. Numerical Meanings of Probabilistic Expressions -- Distributions of Your Own Best Estimate Form A and B Combined, 1987; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-639. Numerical Meanings of Probabilistic Expressions -- Scanning of Your Own Best Estimate, 1987; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-641. Numerical Meanings of Probabilistic Expressions -- Range of Estimates for Others, 1987; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-643. Quantitative Meanings of Verbal Probability Expressions, 1987; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Reagan, Robert Timothy; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-645. Numerical Meanings of Probabilistic Expressions -- Medians of Combined Results for Intensity Functions, 1988; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-648. Introduction to Chapter 8, 1988; Brown, Constance, and Frederick Mosteller (Box 30)
    - Memorandum NS-652. Numerical Meanings of Probabilistic Expressions -- Means (or Medians) and Sample Sizes from 18 Studies (Preliminary), 1988; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-656. Supplement to Memorandum NS-654 (Continuation of Chapter Eight), 1988; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-658. Contiinuation of Fragments of Chapter Ten: Which Denominator?, 1988; Blackwell, T. E., (Thomas E.); Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 31)
      Follows Memo 655.
    - Memorandum NS-659. Box for the ANOVA Book on Stokes' Nationalization of Electoral Forces, 1988; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-660. Confidence Intervals for Variance Components, 1988; Brown, Constance (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-661. Introductory Material for Chapter Eight, 1988; Tukey, John W., (John Wilder), 1915-2000 (Box 31)
      To immediately precede Memos 648-651, 654, 656.
    - Memorandum NS-662. New Introduction for Chapter Four, 1988; Schmid, Christopher H (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-663. Reanalysis by Contrasts of Two Two-Way Designs, 1988; Schmid, Christopher H (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-664. Transformation in Three-Way and More-Way Designs, 1988; Emerson, John D. (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-665. Matching Transformations, 1988; Emerson, John D. (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-666. Some Issues for Discussion in ANOVA Project, 1988; Emerson, John D.; Schmid, Christopher H (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-667. Letter to Hoaglin and Mosteller about Future Grant Proposals and My Leave, 1988; Emerson, John D. (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-668. Inflation of R 2 and F, 1988; Emerson, John D. (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-669. Introduction to Transformation, 1988; Emerson, John D. (Box 31)
      Replaces Memo 662
    - Memorandum NS-671. Components of Variance, 1988; Brown, Constance; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 31)
      Revises and combines Memos 634, 640, 646, 648-651, 654, 656, 659-661.
    - Memorandum NS-672. Transformation in Three-Way and More-Way Designs, 1988; Emerson, John D. (Box 31)
      Replaces Memo 664
    - Memorandum NS-673. Reservations about Our Strategy for Valve Splitting, 1988; Emerson, John D. (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-674. Part of Chapter Four, 1988; Schmid, Christopher H (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-675. Matching Transformations, 1988; Emerson, John D. (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-677. Summary of where ANOVA Work Stands, 1988; Emerson, John D. (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-678. Possible Fragment on the Rothamsted Uniformity Trial, 1988; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 31)
    - Memorandum NS-679. Reformulation in Analysis of Variance, 1988; Emerson, John D. (Box 31)
      Replaces Memos 625-627.
    - Memorandum NS-680. Continuation of Fragments of Chapter 10: Which Denominator?, 1988; Blackwell, T. E., (Thomas E.); Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 31)
      Follows Memo 655. Revises Memo 658 slightly and adds material to it.
    - Memorandum NS-681. Cube-Square Problem, 1983-1987; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 32)
      Memo and notes. See also: Series I, David Penney.
    - Memorandum NS-683. Downsweeping, 1988; Rosenberger, James L., 1946- (Box 32)
    - Memorandum NS-684. Method of Moments Estimation of Variance Components with Two-Way Analysis of Variance, 1988; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 32)
    - Memorandum NS-685. Box on Several Treatments Applied to Litters of Unequal Size, 1988; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 32)
    - Memorandum NS-687. Final Downsweeping: The Use of Paull's Rule for Aggregation, 1988; De Veaux, Richard D.; Goodall, Colin Robert (Box 32)
    - Memorandum NS-688. Example for Chapter Eight, 1988; Brown, Constance (Box 32)
      To follow page D-11 of Chapter Eight
    - Memorandum NS-689. Possible Fragment on the Rothamsted Uniformity Trial for Chapter Ten, 1988; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 32)
    - Memorandum NS-690. Method of Moments Estimation of Variance Components with Two-Way Analysis of Variance, Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 32)
      Fragment for Chapter Ten